Mr, Isaac Kelechi

Full Stack Developer

Profile

Full Stack Developer with 5+ years of experience from creating, designing and managing web & mobile applications. Proficient with developing database, creating user interfaces, writing and testing code, debugging issues, implementing new features based on user feedback and collaborating with any teams to develop a product.

Professional Experience

Jun 2021 – present Port Harcourt, Nigeria	 Full Stack Developer, Quelib Created and implemented a full working mobile application from scratch to production with both back-end and front-end Marketed and Advertised the app via Facebook and Twitter and getting over 200% increase in users
Nov 2021 – Mar 2022 Ikeja Lagos, Nigeria	 Mobile App Developer, FoodNow Identify, analyzed and debugged app issues with both back-end and front-end developers on the team. Recreated, Designed & maintained the app. Completely worked with the team to create a functional client app
Nov 2020 – May 2021 Port Harcourt, Nigeria	 Full Stack Developer, Ohms Created the wireframe and designed the app using flutter framework Developed the backend using php mysql and connected to the frontend using restful api
Oct 2019 – Nov 2020 Port Harcourt, Nigeria	 Full Stack Developer, Albaama Used HTML CSS to create an ecommerce website with stunning UI and great User experience Completely created am admin section with full functional using php mysql

Education

Sep 201	7
Bauchi,	Nigeria

Abubakar Tafewa Belewa University, Computer Science

Skills

HTML	• • • •	CSS	• • • • •
JavaScript	• • • • •	React.js (TypeScript)	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$
Flutter	• • • •	PHP	• • • •
Node.js	• • • • •	MySql	• • • •
MongoDB	• • • • •	Firebase	••••
Git & Github	• • • •	Adobe illustrator	••••
Figma	• • • • •	Rest Api	••••